<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Diablo Wiki</string>
    <string name="main_quote">\"Many moons have passed since I left the town of Tristram behind me.
        Since then I\'ve tried to forget the terrors I beheld beneath the cold earth, and the twisted nightmares that have haunted my every waking moment.
        There\’s something dark within me now; I can feel it, driving me towards the East, assuring me that my salvation lies within the ruins of ancient kingdoms.
        Though I know the way, I know not what perils will arise to hinder my journey, and as I pass through the first gate,
        I know that the better part of my soul will remain behind… forever.\" \n\n— The Dark Wanderer </string>
    <string name="main_intro">Diablo was a best seller series and following its popularity,
        although unofficial, was an expansion pack, entitled Diablo: Hellfire,
        which was released by Sierra Entertainment in 1997. \nThis was followed by a true sequel,
        Diablo II, which was released by Blizzard in 2000.
        \nDiablo (otherwise known as Diablo I) is an action-adventure game developed by Blizzard North and released by Blizzard Entertainment on December 31, 1996.

        \n\nSet in the kingdom of Khanduras that is located in the world of Sanctuary,
        Diablo has the player take control of a lone hero or heroine starting outside of their house in town as they set out on a journey to rid the town of Tristram of the titular Lord of Terror,
        and his horde of demon minions lurking in the shadows underground beneath the Cathedral at the very edge of town.
    </string>
    <string name="main_intro2">
        \n\nDiablo II, the sequel to the popular game Diablo, is a dark, fantasy-themed action role-playing game in a hack-and-slash or "dungeon roaming" style.
        \nAfter the Stress Test in spring 2000, it was released for both Microsoft Windows and Mac OS in the summer 2000 by Blizzard Entertainment.
        \nDiablo II was developed by Blizzard North.

        \n\nBy April 2001, Diablo II had become one of the most popular online games of all time.
        \nMajor factors that contributed to Diablo II\'s success include what fans found to be addictive hack-and-slash gameplay and free access to Battle.net.
        \nDiablo II may be played as a single-player game, multi-player via a LAN, or multi-player via Battle.net, with the last option being the most popular one.

        \n\nThe game was conceptualized and designed by Stieg Hedlund, along with Blizzard North founders David Brevik, Max and Erich Schaefer acting as project heads for the other disciplines.
        \nThe main production roles were handled by Matthew Householder and Bill Roper.

        \n\nAn expansion, Diablo II: Lord of Destruction, was released in 2001.</string>

    <string name="header_intro">Introduction to Diablo Saga</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_logo1">Initial image content_main</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_logo2">Second image content_main</string>
    <string name="nav_about_game">About the game</string>
    <string name="nav_lore">Lore</string>
    <string name="nav_lore_diablo1">Diablo I</string>
    <string name="nav_lore_diablo2">Diablo II</string>
    <string name="nav_characters">Characters</string>
    <string name="nav_items">Items</string>
    <string name="nav_talents">Talents</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="place_holder">Place holder</string>
    <string name="header_image">Header image</string>
</resources>