<resources>

    <!-- /////////////////////////// LORE /////////////////////////// -->

    <string name="app_name">Diablo Wiki</string>
    <string name="first_quote">\"Many moons have passed since I left the town of Tristram behind me.
        Since then I\'ve tried to forget the terrors I beheld beneath the cold earth, and the twisted nightmares that have haunted my every waking moment.
        There\’s something dark within me now; I can feel it, driving me towards the East, assuring me that my salvation lies within the ruins of ancient kingdoms.
        Though I know the way, I know not what perils will arise to hinder my journey, and as I pass through the first gate,
        I know that the better part of my soul will remain behind… forever.\" \n\n— The Dark Wanderer </string>
    <string name="first_intro">Diablo was a best seller series and following its popularity,
        although unofficial, was an expansion pack, entitled
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Diablo:_Hellfire">Diablo: Hellfire</a>,
        which was released by Sierra Entertainment in 1997. \nThis was followed by a true sequel,
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Diablo_II">Diablo II</a>, which was released by Blizzard in 2000.
        Diablo (otherwise known as Diablo I) is an action-adventure game developed by
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Blizzard_North">Blizzard North</a> and released by
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Blizzard_Entertainment">Blizzard Entertainment</a> on December 31, 1996.

        \n\nSet in the kingdom of
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Khanduras">Khanduras</a> that is located in the world of
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Sanctuary">Sanctuary</a>,
        Diablo has the player take control of a lone hero or heroine starting outside of their house in town as they set out on a journey to rid the town of
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Tristram">Tristram</a> of the titular <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Diablo">Lord of Terror</a>,
        and his horde of demon minions lurking in the shadows underground beneath the
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Diablo_I_Walkthrough#The_Cathedral.2FDungeon">Cathedral</a> at the very edge of town.
    </string>
    <string name="first_intro2">
        \n\n<a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Diablo_II">Diablo II</a>
        , the sequel to the popular game
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Diablo_(Game)">Diablo</a>
        , is a dark, fantasy-themed action role-playing game in a hack-and-slash or "dungeon roaming" style.
        After the Stress Test in spring 2000, it was released for both Microsoft Windows and Mac OS in the summer 2000 by
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Blizzard_Entertainment">Blizzard Entertainment</a>.
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Diablo_(Game)">Diablo</a> was developed by Blizzard North.

        \n\nBy April 2001,
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Diablo_II">Diablo II</a>
        had become one of the most popular online games of all time.
        Major factors that contributed to
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Diablo_II">Diablo II\'s</a>
        success include what fans found to be addictive hack-and-slash gameplay and free access to
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Battle.net">Battle.net</a>.
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Diablo_II">Diablo II</a>
        may be played as a single-player game, multi-player via a LAN, or multi-player via
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Battle.net">Battle.net</a>, with the last option being the most popular one.

        \n\nThe game was conceptualized and designed by
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Stieg_Hedlund">Stieg Hedlund</a>, along with
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Blizzard_North">Blizzard North</a>
        David Brevik, Max and Erich Schaefer acting as project heads for the other disciplines.
        The main production roles were handled by Matthew Householder and Bill Roper.

        \n\nAn expansion,
        <a href="https://diablo.fandom.com/wiki/Diablo_II:_Lord_of_Destruction">Diablo II: Lord of Destruction</a>
        , was released in 2001.
    </string>
    <string name="lore_summary">The Diablo Universe involves angels, demons, super humans, giant spiders, world-bearing dragons,
        an earth that shouldn\'t rightly exist, necromancy, shape shifting druids, maddened kings, and warring nations: getting lost in it can be easy.
        This article sums up the very basics of events in chronological order, starting from the very birth of reality and ending with what is known for fact.
        It also aims to summarize the most important facts that we know of regarding the backstory that will set the base for Diablo III.

        \n\nSPOILER ALERT: While all articles in this wiki are prone to spoilers, this page will reveal basically all plots and story elements of all games and books released to date.
        It is therefore probably safe to say that it is the most spoiler-intensive article in the wiki. If you do not wish to have your reading or playing experience spoiled, do not read this article.
    </string>
    <string name="the_beginning_of_the_great_conflict">
        Since the birth of reality itself, the High Heavens and the Burning Hells have waged an endless war for anything of value within their realms of order and chaos.
        No side has gained much of anything at all for long, and, in their struggle, have often destroyed much of what they sought to claim.
        It is referred to as The Great Conflict, and all other wars and events, like The Sin War, fall under it.

        \n\nThe story begins with Inarius, a powerful angel and member of the Angiris Council.
        Tired of the constant fighting, he sees little point in their infinite war they are waging against Hell.
        Convinced that there must be others such as him in both Heaven and Hell, Inarius starts to search for other individuals who share his views on the war.
        To his surprise there are many such as himself, and together with Lilith, daughter of Mephisto, he leads a great exodus.
        Together, they defect from Heaven and Hell and search for another place to live.
        They succeed in stealing the Worldstone, and perform two tasks which above all others will affect the course of history:

        \n\n - Create Sanctuary, the world of men, as a paradise and refuge from the Great Conflict
        \n - Create the Nephalem, the first humans

        \n\nTo protect this world from both Heaven and Hell, they used the stolen Worldstone.
        It acted as a protective barrier, and effectively prevented angels and demons from either directly invading Sanctuary or noticing its existence at all.
        How exactly it worked remains unclear, but work it did.

        \n\nThe two races of Heaven and Hell tried to live peacefully with each other on Sanctuary, and even mated with each other,
        spawning the first generation of humans, called the Nephalem.
        It quickly became apparent that the Nephalem were as powerful as their parents, and had the potential to be much, much more than any angel or demon.
        This caused struggle among the higher beings. Inarius wanted to kill the humans, as he viewed them as a threat to their own existence.
        Lilith, on the other hand, wanted to raise the Nephalem to an army and have them fight both Heaven and Hell.
        The two began fighting, and Inarius cast out Lilith from Sanctuary and imprisoned her in The Void, claiming Sanctuary as his own.
        Many of the Nephalem were slain during this time, but some survived, like Bul-Kathos and Rathma.
        The latter became the servant of Trag\'Oul, a mystical dragon, and guardian of Sanctuary.
    </string>
    <string name="the_sin_war">
        As time went on, the Prime Evils discovered Sanctuary.
        Immediately realizing the potential of humanity as a weapon against Heaven, they created a religion called The Triune there to lure humans to their side.
        Inarius thus similarly set up his own Cathedral of Light to combat the Three.
        The two forces battled behind the scenes with each other on Sanctuary, while Heaven remained unknowing of Sanctuary\'s existence.
        The two religions waged a constant but seemingly petty war against each other, and the world was more or less unaffected.
        The two churches meddled in the everyday lives of humans sometimes, but none except for the most high-ranking of the church servants knew the true identities between the religions.
        That all changed when Lilith broke free of her prison. Returning to Sanctuary, she once again sought to use the humans to her own advantage and conquer both Heaven and Hell.

        \n\nIn these events, a man named Uldyssian, a distant descendant of Inarius and Lilith, got caught in her plots.
        Unbeknownst to him, Lilith gave him magical powers and framed him. Making it appear as though he had slain the servants of both the Triune,
        and the Cathedral of Light. Lilith disguised herself as a human named Lylia, and snared Uldyssian into doing as she wished.
        Uldyssian thought that these powers lay latent in all humans, and, followed by Mendeln, his younger brother, Serenthia,
        a longtime family friend infatuated with Uldyssian and the daughter of the merchant Cyrus, and Achilios, a childhood friend and archer,
        fled the town of Seram fearing for their lives. The very people who were once close friends and neighbors turned upon Uldyssian fearing his new abilities,
        and what it seemed that he did with them. Uldyssian blamed the Triune, and the Cathedral for the predicament he was in and so set off to awaken these powers in others,
        that they might live in a world of their own crafting, not the Triune or Cathedral. The venture was a struggle at first, but with the unknown aid from Lilith,
        more and more people were found who could use magic, and they gathered under Uldyssian. They became known as the Edyrem, with Uldyssian as their leader.

        \n\nThese actions brought with them turmoil. Lucion, leader of the Triune and son of Mephisto, sent formidable enemies to hunt down Uldyssian,
        among them Malic, Damos, Gulag and Astrogha (the latter who also appears in other novels, most notably Moon of the Spider).

        \n\nMendeln, during this time, was noticed by Rathma. Rathma was the son of Inarius and Lilith, and the first servant of Trag\'Oul,
        a great dragon connected to Sanctuary but aligned with neither Heaven nor Hell. Rathma trained Mendeln as an apprentice, and they are the first two Necromancers.

        \n\nLilith in the meantime understood that her plans could not be achieved unless something was done with the Worldstone.
        The crystal had been created by Inarius to both shield the world and to limit the powers of humans.
        So long as it still stood, no human army of hers would ever wage war with Heaven or Hell.
        Uldyssian however was brought there, and after a brief brawl with Bul\'Kathos, he was allowed into the Worldstone Chamber with Rathma as his companion.
        After killing bat-like demons Rathma, though doubtful he would succeed, suggested Uldyssian attempt to change the worldstone to better favor him and his people.
        What he did astonished Rathma, and later Inarius as well. Uldyssian had altered the structure of the crystal, something not even Inarius could undo.
        This change had monumental consequences, and not only stopped the weakening of the Nephalem, but in fact sped up the growth of their powers.

        \n\nEventually Inarius was dragged into the conflict.
        The tyrant ruler of Sanctuary, he had considered himself above Uldyssian and refused to come into direct contact with him.
        Because of that belief, he sent his trusted assistant Gamuel to assassinate Uldyssian.
        The plot failed and Inarius resorted to even more desperate measures, a pact with Diablo himself. At this point, the human\'s powers had grown immensely,
        and a confrontation was imminent.
        Initially Inarius did not view Uldyssian as much of a threat, but as his efforts to stop the human continued to fail,
        Inarius became more and more desperate (though he refused to admit as much to himself).
        At this time, Inarius was approached by Diablo, and the Prime Evil offered him a pact. Together the two sought to defeat Uldyssian and his Edyrem.
        At the same time, Tyrael discovered Sanctuary, and soon thereafter the High Heavens was notified of the existence of this world.

        \n\nThe High Heavens viewed Sanctuary and its inhabitants as an abomination to existence, and acted accordingly, sending their armies directly to Sanctuary.
        Trag\'Oul, the guardian of Sanctuary, used his immense power to shield Sanctuary\'s location from the angels but he could not hold it forever.
        Uldyssian and Inarius also clashed, and that battle is without a doubt the fiercest battle that has ever taken place on the face of Sanctuary,
        and likely ever will. Both wielded the strength of gods, and continually changed the landscape surrounding them as they battled. As they fought,
        a tear appeared in the sky as the hosts of angels finally reached and invaded Sanctuary. Soon after, Uldyssian\'s entire body infused with energy,
        he acquired a higher understanding of Sanctuary itself and easily broke the bond between Inarius and the Worldstone.
        Inarius, without the immense amount of power to draw upon was easily defeated by Uldyssian,
        and trapped in a prison until the Angiris Council further decided his fate.
        Soon after the angels reached Sanctuary, Tyrael found Uldyssian and shackled him.
        Demons of the Burning Hells, determined not to let the angels destroy what they sought to exploit, erupted onto the landscape and a three way battle commenced.
        The angels battling on one side, the demons on the other, and the Edyrem stuck in the middle.
        Uldyssian still shackled, was forced to watch his people as they fought against both angel and demon.
        Overcome with emotion, he finally broke free of Tyrael\'s bonds and demanded the armies to stop.
        Surprisingly, they all became frozen in time. Uldyssian then cleared the angels and the demons from his world.
        He began changing the landscape back to how it was before all the destruction had taken place.
        As he did so, his powers refused to cooperate and instead destroyed the environment where he was trying to fix it.
        He realized the only thing he could do was to draw the destruction into himself, and so with all his might he did so.
        Finally, after taking in all the destruction that Sanctuary had suffered, Trag\'Oul guided him to The Void to release it.

        \n\nHe felt the pressure building up again, this time for the final moment, and readied himself and his world for it.
        And when it came, it did so with an explosion of pure energy that ever so briefly shook Sanctuary to its foundations.
        Uldyssian roared, not because of pain but rather the sheer ecstasy of his transformation.
        He was no longer a mere human but something of which even the angels and demons could not conceive.
        He was Sanctuary for one moment, and all that surrounded it. His presence dwarfed that of Trag\'Oul… of any being near.
        His consciousness spread out above his treasured world, where he looked at it one last time.
    </string>
    <string name="the_reset">
        After the battle, a gathering was held between the Angiris Council and Mephisto.
        Sanctuary was all but destroyed, but all hope was not lost. Some, like Rathma, pleaded with Heaven to spare Sanctuary.
        A vote was held between the Angels. Imperius voted against Sanctuary\'s existence and Auriel argued strongly for it.
        The deciding vote was laid by Tyrael, who initially seemed to show little love for humanity,
        something which has evidently developed over the years since this event. Together with Mephisto, a deal was made between Heaven and Hell.
        Sanctuary was to live on its own, with no war brought there by Heaven or Hell. Humanity would choose for themselves what to do.
        In return for agreeing to this, Mephisto obtained custody of Inarius and took him to the Burning Hells.
        Mephisto sought Inarius because it was him and his daughter Lilith that was responsible for the creation of Sanctuary and the Nephalem.

        \n\nThis was followed by a reset of the world. Time was reverted right to the point where Uldyssian left his home village,
        and events were unmade so that the inhabitants of Sanctuary could mature on their own, without the influence of the Triune, or the Cathedral.

        \n\n - All memories were wiped save that of the original Nephalem
        (the reasoning was that the original Nephalem were very few and they would pass-on soon enough anyway) and Mendeln
        (Trag\'Oul saved him his memory so he could remember the sacrifice his brother made, as well as teach any willing students the ways of the balance).

        \n\n - Serenthia is revived and Achilios is turned back into a living human because of Uldyssian sacrificing himself
        (this is a direct effect of Uldyssian\'s sacrifice, has nothing to do with the Angiris Council or Mephisto)

        \n\n - The Cathedral and Triune were no more.

        \n\nThis, the reset world, is the past from which the games take place.
        The first \'version\', with Uldyssian, isn\'t recorded in any history but is known by a few humans, as well as angels and demons naturally.
    </string>
    <string name="the_dark_exile">
        Azmodan, Belial, Andariel, and Duriel are the four Lesser Evils of Hell.
        Whether Diablo and his brothers intended for it or not, the Four Lesser Evils plotted and ultimately exiled the Three Primes into Sanctuary.
        In their absence, Belial, the lord of Lies, and Azmodan, the Lord of Sin, engaged in a civil war between themselves.
        Their war rages in the deepest pits of Hell to this day.
    </string>
    <string name="the_horadrim">
    Tyrael learns of the Three\'s exile into Sanctuary and mobilizes to stop them.
    He creates the Horadrim, a collection of the most powerful human Magi, including Jered Cain,
    Deckard Cain\'s ancestor, and Tal Rasha.
    Tyrael charges the Horadrim with the capture of the Three Prime Evils, giving them Soulstones to
    imprison the souls of Diablo and his brothers within.
    One by one they find and imprison the Primes. Unable to permanently destroy the demons, the
    Horadrim are forced to instead hide the Soulstones.
    Their locations are as follows:

    \n\n - Baal\’s Soulstone was imprisoned inside a huge tomb constructed with a single purpose:
    keep him in and others out.
    Baal had damaged his soulstone during his capture due to his destructive nature.
    Tal Rasha, knowing that the final shard of Baal\'s broken Soulstone was not great enough to
    contain the Prime Evil,
    chose to use his own body as a prison for the Prime. Lodging it into his chest and binding
    himself to a pillar,
    Tal Rasha remained in the tomb for centuries, containing the Evil within.

    \n\n - Mephisto\’s Soulstone was sealed inside a temple in Kurast, although he had originally
    been captured in Aranoch along with Baal.
    Afraid to imprison two Primes so close to each other, the Horadrim chose to move him.
    The Zakarum monks were tasked with its protection (ultimately, however, the Soulstone corrupted
    the monks and Mephisto took a host among them).

    \n\nDiablo had fled to the west and continued to evade capture for several decades after his
    brothers\' capture.
    Eventually he was captured near today\'s Westmarch, and the Horadrim built a cathedral above his
    tomb to stand guard.
    As time passed by however, the Horadrim fell apart, and no one else remembered the evil
    imprisoned within.
    </string>

    <!-- /////////////////////////// CLASSES /////////////////////////// -->

    <string name="warrior_tab1">
        Warriors are arguably the strongest character class in Diablo I.
        They can wield Swords, Axes or Maces, and swing them at fast speed with ease.
        These weapons are either one-handed or two-handed.
        Two-handed weapons are more useful in the beginning, but at later levels, players reach a Vitality cap which causes Life to increase at a relatively slower rate.
        In these later levels, the warrior has similar life to their earlier levels, but the monsters do much more damage.
        This necessitates the use of a Shield. Their amazing Strength allows them to equip even the heaviest of all Armor.

        \n\nTheir magical abilities are limited.
        With the lowest maximum Magic of 50 and less Mana per level than the other classes, they are forced to only use support spells like Stone Curse and Teleport.
        With their low mana, these support spells can be used only sparingly.
        Since their low level attack spells cannot effectively damage high-level monsters, attack spells like Firebolt and Charged Bolt are not an option.
        Advocates, which can teleport away from the player(s), and the Succubi, which upon close contact, flee at the exact same pace as the player character(s) walks,
        are for that very reason especially difficult. Following them might result in aggravating more enemies to attack the player(s).
        Although the modification which gives less Light Radius is intended to be a curse, it proves very beneficial to warriors nonetheless.
        If one chooses to go with a lower light radius, the Warrior will aggravate fewer monsters.
        </string>
    <string name="rogue_tab1">
        The Rogue\'s Strength and Magic attributes are intermediate between the Warrior and the Sorcerer,
        but with a Vitality being a bit lower than that of a Warrior and on par with a Sorcerer\'s,
        however her Dexterity is much higher than that of the aforementioned two classes.
        She is the only character class who can use Bows effectively,
        since the other two classes lack the dexterity needed for higher Bow Damage and To Hit percentage and are innately slow at firing Missiles.
        The quantity of Arrows is infinite which means that they will never take an end until the bow itself breaks down, unless it is an Indestructible one,
        and it is of great advantage for her, especially since she uses bows frequently, if she\'s not up for a Shield-and-Sword setup, that is.
        The Rogue\'s strength is mostly used for wearing heavy Plate Armor, since her damage comes as most from her Dexterity,
        nevertheless Strength combined with the formerly mentioned attribute from equipment gives her quite of an increase in damage.

        \n\nRogues are not as effective in team games, since allies can cause damage to one another even with Player Friendly set on. For example;
        if a Warrior is attacking, then the Rogue has to accurately target the monster to avoid hitting the Warrior.
        The only saving grace a Warrior has from accidental damage is his Shield; since there is not a hard cap on Blocking,
        if he were to have enough Dexterity he would be able to block the most of a Rogue\'s arrows, if not every arrow she fires as long as he is immobile.
        </string>
    <string name="sorcerer_tab1">
        Sorcerers are a playable class in Diablo I. They are the game\'s most effective spell casters.
        Since they have the highest maximum Magic out of all the character classes, they can effectively use the high-end spells.
        These high-end spells require more than just a level-one proficiency.
        With the sorcerer\'s naturally high Mana, the class can use spells repeatedly, and the class has the highest casting rate out of any other classes.
        </string>
    <string name="monk_tab1">
        The Monk is a powerful unarmed combatant. They are strong and dextrous.
        Monks have some skill with fighting with staves, and though it does less damage than their bare hands,
        staves enable them to execute a sweeping attack and block incoming blows.
        Likewise, heavy armor actually gives them less defense than lighter armor.
        Since they possess great natural damage already, they search out staves which will give them faster attack.
        Dexterity adds to their damage equally to strength, however Dexterity also increases their ability to block incoming attacks with their staves.
        Their high natural defense makes searching for high defense armor less of a necessity. They try to find armor that gives them effects instead.
        In unarmed combat they prefer to use their feet as weapons rather than their hands. Their kicks are very fast and do a lot of damage at high levels.

        \n\nThe Monk search skill is very useful. In Diablo I, items could not be highlighted on the ground with the magical spell search.
        This caused problems when trying to find rings, amulets or Elixirs on the ground, especially if they fell behind an object.
        This necessitated a tiring search by the player to find the tiny item on the ground.
        The Search spell highlighted not only the item on the ground, but also all items that had fallen on the map.
        Other classes could learn Search as a spell.
        </string>
    <string name="barbarian_tab1">
        The Hellfire Barbarian can only be played after editing the Command.txt file in the Hellfire folder, and only in the 1.01 patch.
        He is similar to the Warrior class and uses the same graphics, but he has unequaled prowess in melee combat, even when reduced to the same tactics as the Warrior,
        at the costs of no innate magic power and reduced chance to-hit.
        </string>
    <string name="bard_tab1">
        The Bard is one of the two unfinished classes in Diablo: Hellfire, the other being the Barbarian.
        She could only be played after editing the Command.txt file in the Hellfire folder.

        \n\nThe Bard uses the Rogue\'s graphic, but can dual-wield weapons in lieu of a shield.
        Bards possess balanced attributes, so they excel at nothing.
        Possessing medium amounts of the three core attributes of Dexterity, Strength and Magic,
        while enough to make them able to at least make use of everything in the game, for the purposes of specialization, makes them weak at all of them.
        High dexterity, while helpful when using bows, works better when the bard makes use of at least one sword.

        \n\nBards have the ability to wield two one-handed weapons. This combination of two one-handed swords is not as powerful as it seems.
        It can be as damaging as a Great Axe at best. But there are benefits to this style for her.
        To name one, there is the potential for an additional two magical modifications on the second weapon, which allows for deadly combos.
        Equipping a Civerb\'s Cudgel along with a good sword (preferably of Speed or Haste)
        will make the Bard a very powerful Melee character since the +200% damage bonus on Civerb\'s Cudgel applies to the whole damage and not just weapon damage.
        On the other hand, a Bard could sacrifice stopping power for a good weapon with life steal, and it would be near impossible to end her reign, unless stunlock is involved.

        \n\nAnother benefit is that when a Bard dual wields, she possesses the same ability to attack enemies adjacent to her target that the Monk has with his staff.
        This, when combined with potent equipment, allows the Bard to carve a path of destruction with relative ease,
        much in the same way that the Barbarian would with his trusty axe.

        \n\nA fatal flaw in this character\'s design is that she has the melee attack speed of the Rogue.
        Rogues were never intended to be melee attackers, so they were given a slower melee attack speed than the warrior.
        The only saving grace of the bard\'s melee ability is her high dexterity; having a higher degree of dexterity,
        as well as being able to equip a second weapon for extra to-hit makes the bard more suited for Civerb\'s Cudgel than the Warrior or Barbarian, who firstly,
        needed to get the extra To-Hit from jewelry when wielding it, and secondly, had to make the hits count, as they swung at their normal attacking speed,
        robbing them of being able to stunlock some monsters. By hitting the enemy more frequently, she has the potential to stun lock her enemy.

        \n\nBecause her magical ability is only second to the sorcerer, a Bard can effectively use the attacking magical spells of Chain Lightning and Fireball,
        and some may even find worth in choosing to invoke the protection of Mana Shield. This helps to made the Bard effective in combat, both as a spellcaster,
        and as a melee hero who can quickly restore damage taken with her equipment and the art of healing.

        \n\nHowever, the saying \'jack of all trades, masters of none\' certainly applies to a Bard: a Warrior, Monk, or Barbarian will always outdamage her in melee combat,
        the Rogue bests her in ranged combat, and the Sorcerer is more powerful in spell combat.
        Their strength lies in their ability to adapt: if a Bard cannot adapt, death and/or failure is more likely.
        </string>

    <string name="amazon_tab2">
        The Amazon is a powerful woman warrior of the Askari, who belongs to nomadic bands who roam the plains near the South Sea.
        The wandering of these groups often brings them into conflict with other peoples, so the Amazon is accustomed to fighting to defend her own.
        This lifestyle has made her fiercely independent and able to weather severe hardship and travel.
        While her skill with the Bow rivals that of the Rogues, the Amazon is also adept in the use of Spears and Javelins, as well as in hand to hand combat.
        Amazon Weapons are items which only Amazons can equip. These are special Bows, Javelins and Spears.
        The Amazon is much sought after as a mercenary, in which type of service she will be loyal as long as her own ends are also served.
        \nThe Amazon is a playable class in Diablo II. She is voiced by Jessica Straus.
    </string>
    <string name="barbarian_tab2">
        The Barbarians, ones of the members of any of several tribes on the fringes of civilization, rebuff the influence of those they see as soft and weak.
        Ceaseless clan warfare and the constant struggle to survive in the hostile wilderness are evident in the Barbarians\' sturdy and powerful frame.
        Though perhaps lacking the sophistication of their civilized contemporaries, the Barbarians have an acute awareness of their surroundings.
        Because of their shamanistic belief in the animal powers with whom they identify, the Barbarians are sometimes associated with stories of lycanthropy.
        In fact, they believe that they can improve their superb battle tactics by calling upon the totemic animal spirits to infuse themselves with supernatural strengths and abilities.
    </string>
    <string name="necromancer_tab2">
        The Necromancer is one of the most versatile classes in the game.
        He can have the largest number of minions simultaneously for those who love micro-management as well as having extremely potent direct damage spells.
        He can also call upon a variety of different effects via Curses.
    </string>
    <string name="paladin_tab2">
        The Paladin has a variety of builds. It is one of the most adaptable classes having builds that are good for PvM (like Hammerdin) and builds that are good for PvP (like FoHer).
        Paladins (a.k.a. "Knights of the Faith") use holy magic as gifted by the High Heavens.
        They maintain strictly ordered lives, constantly upholding the cause of Virtue and Light.
        They must never succumb to worldly temptations lest they risk being deceived into following \"false lights\" - demons masquerading as Heavenly beings.
        Paladins may use their skills to increase their prowess with sword and shield, as well as cast blessing auras on themselves and to any who join them.
        They are particularly skilled against the undead, as they know many holy incantations effective against these types of creatures.

        \n\nNumerous Paladin orders exist/have existed. The position of \"Paladin\" stems at least as far back as the Protectors of the Word,
        which were formed just prior to Rakkis\'s crusade against the West. Since this time, different sects of Paladins have formed, with separate goals and bases of operation.
        What these orders share in common (in theory at least) is their devotion to the teachings of Akarat and spreading the Zakarum faith.
        By the End of Days however, many Paladin orders had been disbanded. Some formed new orders (such as the Templars), while others went rogue or freelance.
        Others have simply died. While the Knights of Westmarch continue to function, they have distanced themselves from the Zakarum,
        and are more focused on defending Westmarch from physical rather than spiritual harm.

        \n\n\"Dark\" Paladins also exist, who carry the favor of Hell.
        Paladins are required to sanctify their weapons with their own blood.
        This sacrifice is a symbol of faith, that even the lowliest Paladin has to submit before the Light,
        in order that he may prove himself worthy of victory.
    </string>
    <string name="sorceress_tab2">
        Sorceresses are of the Zann Esu Clan. Athletic, affable, and self-assured, Sorceresses hardly seem like scholarly bibliophiles hidden away from civilization.
        They possess many of the same skills as the male members of the Mage Clans, but excel at the use of elemental magic.
        Like most mages, they consider melee combat vulgar, and use magic almost exclusively to fight their enemies.
    </string>
    <string name="assassin_tab2">
        \"Schooled in the martial arts, her mind and body are deadly weapons\"
        \n\nThe Assassin is a character class introduced in Diablo II: Lord of Destruction.
        The Assasin\'s main weapon is a Claw or other such weapon used in the fist such as Katar or Hatchet Hands.
        Assassins are highly adept at lock picking, allowing them to open locked chests without the need for keys used by other classes,
        freeing up precious space in the Assassin\’s inventory for other items.
    </string>
    <string name="druid_tab2">
        The Druid class became playable in Diablo II: Lord of Destruction.
        In terms of play, they are a fairly balanced character, capable of handling themselves as spellcasters,
        with relative proficiency in fire and cold skills, and in melee combat (especially with Shapeshifting skills, not to mention bonuses gained from Spirits).
        They seem to have an affinity for Two-Handed Axes/Maces; a Maul and a Giant Axe, being of Slow Attack Speed for a Barbarian, is Fast Attack Speed for the Druid.
        The other weapons in these groups are adjusted accordingly to respect this affinity.

        \n\nThe Druids shun the use of traditional magic, or Dubhdroiacht, as they call it. Living by the Caoi Dúlra,
        a philosophy that exhorts oneness with the natural world, they instead practice a form of magic based in their close bond to nature.
        Through this intimate kinship with the world of Sanctuary, a Druid has the power to command fire, earth, and the winds.
        Druids are so tied to the natural world that they can call upon the aid of animals and even plants to help them in battle.
        Druids are friends to the animals of the wilds and can call upon them to aid in his struggle.
        They can also use their heightened rapport with the animals to change the shape of their own body,
        drawing on the strengths and abilities of their woodland companions to better serve their cause.
        The most astounding Druid ability is that of shapeshifting,
        allowing them to manipulate their flesh and form to take on the characteristics of the beasts they have sworn to protect.
        Their Barbarian kin (or at least the Henknoc Tribe believe that their ability to form bonds with animals is an ability latent to the Druids\' blood.
        However, throughout their history, the Druids have always fought back against an encroaching wilderness.

        \n\nDruids do not value urban centers in the same way as the Kehjistani.
        They instead dwell in great stone towers (called \'Druid Colleges\'), which are scattered across the land.
        However, Druid villages still exist, and agriculture is practiced.
        Druids generally maintain a calm and reflective demeanor, but the members of this order are not to be trifled with.
        Given their shared ancestry with the Barbarians, they possess great physical strength. By Deckard Cain\'s estimate,
        at least 500 high-ranking warriors watch over and guide much of Druidic culture.
        Druids are willing to do anything to protect their way of life, including risking their own humanity by awakening the beast within.
    </string>


    <!-- /////////////////////////// NAV DRAWER /////////////////////////// -->

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="nav_about_game">About the game</string>
    <string name="nav_lore">Lore</string>
    <string name="nav_lore_diablo1">Diablo I</string>
    <string name="nav_lore_diablo2">Diablo II</string>
    <string name="nav_characters">Characters</string>
    <string name="nav_items">Items</string>
    <string name="nav_talents">Talents</string>

    <string name="place_holder">Place holder</string>
    <string name="header_image">Header image</string>
    <string name="sanctuary_map">Sanctuary Map</string>

    <!-- /////////////////////////// TOOLBAR TITLES //////////////////// -->

    <string name="toolbar_second">Diablo Lore</string>

    <!-- /////////////////////////// HEADERS /////////////////////////// -->

    <string name="header_intro">About Diablo</string>
    <string name="header_the_beginning">The Beginning of the Great Conflict</string>
    <string name="header_the_sin_war">The Sin War</string>
    <string name="header_the_reset">The Reset</string>
    <string name="header_the_dark_exile">The Dark Exile</string>
    <string name="header_the_horadrim">The Horadrim</string>
    <string name="header_diablo_I">Diablo I</string>
    <string name="header_diablo_II">Diablo II</string>
    <string name="header_diablo_II_expansion">Diablo II: Lord of Destruction</string>
    <string name="header_intro_second">Intro</string>
    <string name="header_diablo_lore">Diablo Lore</string>
    <string name="header_warrior_tab1">Warrior</string>
    <string name="header_rogue_tab1">Rogue</string>
    <string name="header_sorcerer_tab1">Sorcerer</string>
    <string name="header_monk_tab1">Monk</string>
    <string name="header_barbarian_tab1">Barbarian</string>
    <string name="header_bard_tab1">Bard</string>
    <string name="header_amazon_tab2">Amazon</string>
    <string name="header_barbarian_tab2">Barbarian</string>
    <string name="header_necromancer_tab2">Necromancer</string>
    <string name="header_paladin_tab2">Paladin</string>
    <string name="header_sorceress_tab2">Sorceress</string>
    <string name="header_assassin_tab2">Assassin</string>
    <string name="header_druid_tab2">Druid</string>

    <!-- /////////////////////////// BUTTONS /////////////////////////// -->

    <string name="intro_button">Intro</string>
    <string name="the_beginning_button">The Beginning</string>
    <string name="the_sin_war_button">The Sin War</string>
    <string name="the_reset_button">The Reset</string>
    <string name="the_dark_exile_button">The Dark Exile</string>
    <string name="the_the_horadrim_button">The The Horadrim</string>
    <string name="button_start">Start</string>
    <string name="button_warrior">Warrior</string>
    <string name="button_bard">Bard</string>
    <string name="button_barbarian">Barbarian</string>
    <string name="button_monk">Monk</string>
    <string name="button_sorcerer">Sorcerer</string>
    <string name="button_rogue">Rogue</string>
    <string name="button_tab1">tab1</string>
    <string name="button_tab2">tab2</string>
    <string name="button_amazon_tab2">Amazon</string>
    <string name="button_barbarian_tab2">Barbarian</string>
    <string name="button_necromancer_tab2">Necromancer</string>
    <string name="button_paladin_tab2">Paladin</string>
    <string name="button_sorceress_tab2">Sorceress</string>
    <string name="button_assassin_tab2">Assassin</string>
    <string name="button_druid_tab2">Druid</string>


    <!-- /////////////////////////// ACTIVITIES /////////////////////////// -->

    <string name="child_activity_third">Third Activity</string>
    <string name="child_activity_second">Second Activity</string>
    <string name="first_home_activity">First/Home Activity</string>

    <!-- /////////////////////////// MENUS /////////////////////////// -->

    <string name="menu_filter">Filter</string>
    <string name="menu_filter_dialog_title">Diablo Weapons Filter</string>

    <string-array name="menu_filter_dialog_options">
        <item>Diablo 1</item>
        <item>Diablo 2</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="menu_filter_dialog_ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="menu_filter_dialog_cancel">Cancel</string>

    <!-- //////////////////////// CONTENT DESCRIPTION ///////////////////// -->

    <string name="go_top_button">Go to the top button</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_logo1">Initial image content_main</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_logo2">Second image content_main</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_1_warrior">Diablo 1 Warrior content description</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_1_rogue">Diablo 1 Rogue content description</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_1_monk">Diablo 1 Monk content description</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_1_monk_attributes">Diablo 1 Monk content description</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_2_amazon_skills">Diablo 2 Amazon skills</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_2_barbarian_skills">Diablo 2 Barbarian skills</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_2_necromancer_skills">Diablo 2 Necromancer skills</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_2_paladin_skills">Diablo 2 Paladin skills</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_2_sorceress_skills">Diablo 2 Sorceress skills</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_2_assassin_skills">Diablo 2 Assassin skills</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_2_druid_skills">Diablo 2 Druid skills</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_2_amazon_attributes">Diablo 2 Amazon attributes</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_2_barbarian_attributes">Diablo 2 Barbarian attributes</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_2_necromancer_attributes">Diablo 2 Necromancer attributes</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_2_paladin_attributes">Diablo 2 Paladin attributes</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_2_sorceress_attributes">Diablo 2 Sorceress attributes</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_2_assassin_attributes">Diablo 2 Assassin attributes</string>
    <string name="contentDescription_diablo_2_druid_attributes">Diablo 2 Druid attributes</string>

    <!-- //////////////////////// THIRD ACTIVITY TAB ////////////////////// -->

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="third_tab_title_1">Diablo I</string>
    <string name="third_tab_title_2">Diablo II</string>

    <!-- //////////////////////// RECYCLERVIEW LAYOUT PLACE HOLDERS ////////////////////// -->

    <string name="weapon_name">Weapon Name</string>
    <string name="weapon_damage">Damage</string>
    <string name="weapon_durability">Durability</string>
    <string name="weapon_requirements">Requirements</string>
    <string name="weapon_price">Price</string>
    <string name="weapon_quality">Quality Level</string>

    <!-- //////////////////////// RECYCLERVIEW LAYOUT WEAPONS ////////////////////// -->

    <string-array name="weapon_image">
        <!-- Diablo 1 -->
        <item>@drawable/small_axe</item>
        <item>@drawable/axe</item>
        <item>@drawable/large_axe</item>
        <item>@drawable/broad_axe</item>
        <item>@drawable/battle_axe</item>
        <item>@drawable/great_axe</item>
        <!-- Diablo 2 -->
        <item>@drawable/hand_axe_d2</item>
        <item>@drawable/axe_d2</item>
        <item>@drawable/double_axe_d2</item>
        <item>@drawable/military_pick_d2</item>
        <item>@drawable/war_axe_d2</item>
        <item>@drawable/large_axe_d2</item>
        <item>@drawable/broad_axe_d2</item>
        <item>@drawable/battle_axe_d2</item>
        <item>@drawable/great_axe_d2</item>
        <item>@drawable/giant_axe_d2</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="weapon">
        <!-- Diablo 1 -->
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Small Axe</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Axe</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Large Axe</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Broad Axe</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Battle Axe</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Great Axe</item>
        <!-- Diablo 2 -->
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Hand Axe</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Axe</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Double Axe</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Military Pick</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">War Axe</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Large Axe</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Broad Axe</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Battle Axe</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Great Axe</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Giant Axe</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="damage">
        <!-- Diablo 1 -->
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Damage: 2–10</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Damage: 4–12</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Damage: 6–16</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Damage: 8–20</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Damage: 10–25</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Damage: 12–30</item>
        <!-- Diablo 2 -->
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Damage: 3–6</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Damage: 4–11</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Damage: 5–13</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Damage: 7–11</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Damage: 10–18</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Damage: 6–13</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Damage: 10–18</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Damage: 12–32</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Damage: 9–30</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Damage: 22–45</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="durability">
        <!-- Diablo 1 -->
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Durability: 24</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Durability: 32</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Durability: 40</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Durability: 50</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Durability: 60</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Durability: 75</item>
        <!-- Diablo 2 -->
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Durability: 28</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Durability: 24</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Durability: 24</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Durability: 26</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Durability: 26</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Durability: 30</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Durability: 35</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Durability: 40</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Durability: 50</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Durability: 50</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="requirements">
        <!-- Diablo 1 -->
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Requirements: None</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Requirements: 22</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Requirements: 30 Strength</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Requirements: 50 Strength</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Requirements: 65 Strength</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Requirements: 80 Strength</item>
        <!-- Diablo 2 -->
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Requirements: None</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Requirements: 32 Strength</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Requirements: 43 Strength</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Requirements: 49 Strength</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Requirements: 67 Strength</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Requirements: 35 Strength</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Requirements: 48 Strength</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Requirements: 54 Strength</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Requirements: 63 Strength</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Requirements: 70 Strength</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="price">
        <!-- Diablo 1 -->
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Price: 150</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Price: 450</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Price: 750</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Price: 1000</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Price: 1500</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Price: 2500</item>
        <!-- Diablo 2 -->
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Price: -</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Price: -</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Price: -</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Price: -</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Price: -</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Price: -</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Price: -</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Price: -</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Price: -</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Price: -</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="quality">
        <!-- Diablo 1 -->
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Quality Level: 2</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Quality Level: 4</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Quality Level: 6</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Quality Level: 8</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Quality Level: 10</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_1">Quality Level: 12</item>
        <!-- Diablo 2 -->
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Quality Level: 3</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Quality Level: 7</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Quality Level: 13</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Quality Level: 19</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Quality Level: 25</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Quality Level: 6</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Quality Level: 12</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Quality Level: 17</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Quality Level: 23</item>
        <item name="axe_diablo_2">Quality Level: 27</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>